export const mockCards = [
	{ id: '1', front: 'Question 1', back: 'Answer 1', nextPractice: new Date(), createdAt: new Date() },
	{ id: '2', front: 'Question 2', back: 'Answer 2', nextPractice: new Date(), createdAt: new Date() },
];


export const reviseMockCards = [
	{
		id: '576f1074-747c-4c44-9932-0e63ee8919c5',
		front: `1. arr.filter(callbackfn)
2. callbackfn is basically a test (word.length>0)
3. parameter for callbackfn => (element, index)
4. truthy values are included

arr.filter((word) => word.length>4) // o/p will be array with words of length greater than 4`,
		back: `1. arr.filter(callbackfn)
2. callbackfn is basically a test (word.length>0)
3. parameter for callbackfn => (element, index)
4. truthy values are included

arr.filter((word) => word.length>4) // o/p will be array with words of length greater than 4
1. arr.filter(callbackfn)
2. callbackfn is basically a test (word.length>0)
3. parameter for callbackfn => (element, index)
4. truthy values are included

arr.filter((word) => word.length>4) // o/p will be array with words of length greater than 4`,
		createdAt: '2024-08-08T22:28:26.000Z',
		nextPractice: '2024-08-08T22:28:26.000Z'
	},
	{
		id: 'ac08fc73-dc65-4577-9eb5-680e9ab1c143',
		front: 'as',
		back: 'sa',
		createdAt: '2024-08-08T22:34:46.000Z',
		nextPractice: '2024-08-08T22:34:46.000Z'
	},
	{
		id: '35d59579-2b46-4128-a3bd-e0c6e913fdf3',
		front: 'as',
		back: 'as',
		createdAt: '2024-08-08T22:36:17.000Z',
		nextPractice: '2024-08-08T22:36:17.000Z'
	},
	{
		id: '6ed86d20-4e9d-40f4-9db2-1ccac098a98d',
		front: 'as',
		back: 'sa',
		createdAt: '2024-08-08T22:38:31.000Z',
		nextPractice: '2024-08-08T22:38:31.000Z'
	},
	{
		id: 'fc19c145-c2db-4c0e-bbfb-fbcad4fc2de9',
		front: 'a',
		back: 's',
		createdAt: '2024-08-08T22:39:26.000Z',
		nextPractice: '2024-08-08T22:39:26.000Z'
	},
	{
		id: '576f1074-747c-4c44-9932-0e63ee8919c1',
		front: 'sanya',
		back: 'as',
		createdAt: '2024-08-08T22:28:26.000Z',
		nextPractice: '2024-08-08T22:28:26.000Z'
	},
	{
		id: 'ac08fc73-dc65-4577-9eb5-680e9ab1c142',
		front: 'as',
		back: 'sa',
		createdAt: '2024-08-08T22:34:46.000Z',
		nextPractice: '2024-08-10T22:34:46.000Z'
	},
	{
		id: '35d59579-2b46-4128-a3bd-e0c6e913fda3',
		front: 'as',
		back: 'as',
		createdAt: '2024-08-08T22:36:17.000Z',
		nextPractice: '2024-08-08T22:36:17.000Z'
	},
	{
		id: '6ed86d20-4e9d-40f4-9db2-1ccac098a18d',
		front: 'as',
		back: 'sa',
		createdAt: '2024-08-08T22:38:31.000Z',
		nextPractice: '2024-08-10T22:38:31.000Z'
	},
	{
		id: 'fc19c145-c2db-4c0e-bbfb-fbcad4fcade9',
		front: 'a',
		back: 's',
		createdAt: '2024-08-08T22:39:26.000Z',
		nextPractice: '2024-08-08T22:39:26.000Z'
	}
]
